You want to master
a new Jutsu right now?
(ガマ吉)新術を
今すぐ完成させたいじゃと？
That's impossible!
お前 そりゃムチャっていうもんじゃ。
(ナルト)ムチャでもなんでも➡
I don't care! I have to do it!
やるっきゃねえんだって！
All right.
よし ちと荒療治になるが
試してみるか。
These will be somewhat
harsh measures, but let's try.
Ohh! Do you have any ideas?
おぉ なんか作戦があるのか？
You... get into Gamatatsu's mouth.
(ガマ吉)オメエ ガマ竜の口の中に入れ。
ハァ？
Huh?!
(カカシ)問題は オレたちだな。
What about us?
The enemy already knows about us.
敵は すでに
こっちの存在に気づいている。
They could take action at any moment.
いつ動きだしても
おかしくない状況だ。
It's possible they'd leave
(ヒナタ)考えられる敵の動きは
ムダな接触を避け 逃走するか➡
to avoid wasting time contacting us
or provoking a fight...
仕掛けてくるか…。
(キバ)どっちにせよ➡
In either case,
our mission is to capture
the enemy and obtain information.
オレたちの任務は 相手を捕獲し
情報を入手することだぜ。
If we lose track of the enemy,
(キバ)万一 相手を
見失うようなことがあれば➡
それは 後々
木ノ葉のリスクになるかもしれねえ。
they may pose a threat
to the Hidden Leaf later.
We'll keep searching for the enemy.
(ヒナタ)索敵を続けます。
(カカシ)そうだな。
Right.
(紅蓮)よく聞きな 野郎ども。
Listen, guys!
Orochimaru-sama gave us
an important mission.
大蛇丸様から ありがたい任務を
賜ったよ。
That is, we're responsible for
delivering him safely to the lake.
(紅蓮)コイツを無事
ある湖まで送り届けること。
We can't afford to fail!
絶対に失敗は許されないよ。
But... I know some strangers
are following us from the hideout.
(紅蓮)だが 妙な連中が
アジトから追ってきてるようだな。
That's just what I'd expect
from you, Guren-san.
(麟児)いやぁ さすがは紅蓮さん。
すでに ご存じとは。
You're already aware of them.
Currently three people and one dog
are a couple of kilometers away,
(麟児)
現在 ３人と１匹が数キロ先の森を➡
ゆっくりではありますが
こちらに向かっているようです。
and they're slowly heading towards us.
What should we do?
どうします？
I know just the thing.
決まってる。
I don't want them to
follow us anymore.
そんな連中に
いつまでも ついてこられちゃ➡
たまらないからな。 ヤツらを捜せ！
ここで潰しておく！
Find them! I'll defeat them here!
you've gotta be extra careful
mijika ni aru mono
with the things nearest to you
tsuneni ki wo tsukete inai to
you know the closer you get to something
amari ni chika sugite
the tougher it is to see it
miushinatte shimai sou
explain to me this happiness
anata ga saikin taiken shita
that you just got to experience?
shiawase wa ittai nan desu ka
or maybe you're so blessed
megumare sugite ite
that you can't even remember it
omoidasenai kamo
that you stand here now
ima koko ni iru koto
that you still live and breathe
iki wo shite iru koto
I realised that they all were miracles
tada soredake no koto ga
just by themselves
kiseki da to kidzuku
you've gotta be extra careful
mijika ni aru mono
with the things nearest to you
tsuneni ki wo tsukete inai to
you know the closer you get to something
amari ni chika sugite
the tougher it is to see it
miushinatte shimai sou
you know the closer you get to something
the tougher it is to see it
and i'll never take it for granted
it's fine to say you'll never give up
oi tsudzukete kita yume
and to keep chasing your dreams
akiramezu ni susumeyo nante
but the more time you spend talking big
kirei goto wo ieru hodo
the less you get done
nanimo dekicha inai kedo
I will press that handful of courage against my heart
hito nigiri no yuuki wo mune ni
and with its help survive another day
ashita wo ikinuku tame ni
and i'll never take it for granted
let's go
The Unseeing Enemy
ハァ ハァ…。
よし！ なんかできそうな気が
してきたってばよ！
All right! I kind of feel like
I can do it!
その意気じゃけえ ナルト。
That's the spirit, Naruto.
All right! Gamatatsu, one more time.
よっしゃ ガマ竜！
もうひとつ頼むぜ。
(ガマ竜)モゴモゴ… うん… ムム…。
よしっ。
All right...
《感じるんだ。 ガマ竜のチャクラを》
I feel it...
Gamatatsu's Chakra!
《一気にためて吐き出す
そのときを》
When he stores it up and spits it out...
ウオォ～！
ホエ？
おっ おお～。
ナルト 大丈夫か？
Naruto, are you all right?!
でも今 なんか
つかんだ気がするってばよ。
I think I just got some sort of clue!
そうか。
《フン。
こりゃおもろうなってきたのぉ》
I see!
Things have gotten interesting...
All right! I've got to practice while
the sensation's still fresh...
よし 今の感じを忘れないうちに
おさらいだってばよ。
Naruto!
(サクラ)ナルト～！
(ガマ竜/ガマ吉)ん？
- Huh?
Oh! Sakura-chan!
あ サクラちゃん。
Come on! Don't waste your time here!
(サクラ)もう アンタ こんなところで
油売ってるんじゃないわよ。
ん？
You smell terrible.
なんか生臭い。
Anyway, why are you so sticky
and worn out?!
っつ～か なんでアンタ
そんなに ベトベトのヨレヨレなわけ？
いや あの これはさ…
今 すんげえ大事なところで…。
Well, umm, this is...
This is really  important...
Anyway, everyone's tired
of waiting for you!
(サクラ)とにかく みんな
待ちくたびれてるんだから。
Let's go!
行くわよ。
あぁ ちょっと待って サクラちゃん。
W-W-W-W-W-Wait a second, Sakura-chan!
I need to practice right now--!
今 おさらいを。
問答無用！
No excuses!
Gamakichi, Gamatatsu...
ガマ吉 ガマ竜 絶対また呼ぶからな！
I'll call you again...!
お… おぅ。 気張れや。
Huh? Sure.
Work hard.
兄ちゃん 口直ししていい？
Nii-chan, can I clean out my mouth?
とらえました！
I sense him!
This is a Ninja's Chakra.
このチャクラの感じ… 忍です！
(ヒナタ)危ない！
Look out!
(牛頭)お前が頭か～っ!! フンッ！
So you're their leader!
カカシ先生っ!!
Kakashi-sensei!
先生！
ダメ キバ君！
Sensei!
Don't, Kiba-kun!
なにっ!?
What?!
(麟児)外したか。
I missed.
でも まぁ 牛頭のヤツが大将を
引き受けてくれたおかげで➡
But since Gozu is taking care
of their boss,
楽ができそうだ。
it looks like things will be easy.
お前ら なかなかの探索能力だよ。
You've got quite the tracking ability...
It really is unfortunate.
実に惜しいところまで
いったんだがな…。
もしかして… この人たち…。
Could it be... Is it them?
あぁ たぶん…
あのアジトにいた連中だ。
Yeah. Probably...
They were in that hideout.
気をつけろよ いいな。
Be careful, okay?
うん… 相手は３人だよ。
どうする キバ君。
Okay, we're against three people.
What should we do, Kiba-kun?
(キバ)オレと赤丸の術は
連動してるからな。
Akamaru and my Jutsu are linked.
まずは 先手必勝だ。
We've got to defeat one of them first
and reduce their numbers.
１人倒して 敵の数を減らす…。
そのあとは？
And after that?
It would be good if we could
defeat them by ourselves,
オレらだけで 倒せりゃいいが…。
まずは カカシ先生が来るまでの
持久戦に持ち込むのが➡
but it'll be best if we can prolong
the battle until Kakashi-sensei comes.
ベストってとこだろうな。
(ヒナタ)了解。
Okay.
《キバ : 狙うのは
手前の２人のいずれかだが…➡
We need to go after one
of the two in front...
見るからに何か仕込んでそうな
マスク野郎は避けとくか…。
But from what I can see,
we should avoid that masked guy.
He looks like he's hiding something.
…となると》
Which means...
行くぜ 赤丸！
(赤丸)ワンッ！
Let's go, Akamaru!
(キバ)牙通牙!!
Fang Over Fang!
鬼霧 煙幕。
Kigiri, smoke screen!
キバ君！
Kiba-kun!
クソッ！ 毒霧か…。
Crap! Poison Mist?!
ワンワン！
そうか サンキュー 赤丸！
I see. Thank you, Akamaru!
《だが 毒じゃねえってことは
ただの目くらましか…》
But does the fact that
it's not poisonous...
mean that it's just a diversion?
《なに… これは!?》
What--?! What's this?!
辺りのにおいが…
全部 消えただと…。
The smells around me... disappeared...?
《そうか… 連中は
これを使って➡
I see.
They use this to erase traces
of their movements...
移動中の痕跡を消してたわけか》
うわっ！
This is bad...
《まずいぜ…
視界がダメな上に 嗅覚まで…》
Aside from the fact that I can't see,
I can't smell anything either...
《待てよ
相手も条件は同じはず…➡
Wait. It should be the same
for our enemies as well.
So how do they know exactly
where I am?!
なのに なんでヤツら 正確に
オレの居場所がわかるんだ!?》
行け 濡羅吏！
Go, Nurari!
《やられる…》
They're going to get me!
伏せてっ！
Duck!
ヒナタか!?
Hinata?!
キバ君 下がってて！
Stand back, Kiba-kun!
ここは私が…。
I'll handle this...
気をつけろ ヒナタ！
Be careful, Hinata!
どんなカラクリか知らねえが➡
I'm not sure how,
but they can move freely in this smoke!
こいつら この煙幕の中でも
自在に動けるらしい。
大丈夫！
視覚と嗅覚が奪われても➡
It's all right!
Even if they take away my sense
of sight and smell,
私の白眼は奪えない！
they cannot take away my Byakugan!
(キバ)わかった。 さがれ 赤丸。
All right.
Stand back, Akamaru!
あなたの相手は 私よ！
I'm your opponent...
What?! Could it be that even
in this smoke screen...?
なんだと!?
お前 まさか この煙幕の中…。
そうよ
あなたの攻撃は すべて見える！
That's right.
I can see all of your attacks!
Right here!
(ヒナタ)ここよ！
うあ～っ！
(濡羅吏)なんてな…。
Just kidding.
(ヒナタ)まさか はずした!?
It can't be! I missed?!
キャッ！
《ヒナタ : そんなはずはないわ。
でも どうして…。
That's impossible. But how?!
これは!?》
What's this...?
(ヒナタ)キャ～ッ!!
《うっ… なんて力だ》
What strength!
フン！
Die!
死ね！
ぐあっ！
(牛頭)影分身か…。
(カカシ)正解。
A Shadow Clone...
Correct.
お前みたいな
ヤバそうなヤツと➡
I can't fight someone as
dangerous as you right away.
いきなり
組み合うわけないでしょ。
(カカシ)
その 限界を超えた筋肉の強化。
You've enhanced your muscles
to their limit.
やったのは 大蛇丸かな？
Did Orochimaru do that for you?
(カカシ)ここで逃げても
お前は オレには勝てないよ。
Even if you run away,
you can't defeat me.
見たところ
お前の武器は 速度と力。
From what I can see,
your weapons are your speed
and your strength.
破壊力バツグンのタイプだが
先読みは オレの得意分野でね。
You've got destructive power,
but I specialize in predicting movements.
ムダな抵抗はやめて
一緒に里まで来てもらおうか。
It's pointless to resist.
Come to the village with me.
断る。
I refuse.
始まったみたいだね。
It looks like it's begun...
まずは 敵も味方も
お手並み拝見 と。
First, I need to see how skilled
my enemies and allies are.
じゃ こっちも
仕込みに掛かるとするか。
I should take action as well...
ハァ… ハァ… ハァ…。
残念… 姿が見えたところで
意味なかった。
How unfortunate.
Even though you can see me,
it's pointless.
《ヒナタ : あの人の体
何かに覆われているんだわ。
Something's surrounding his body...
だから いくらチャクラを打ち込んでも
まるで手応えがない》
That's why he's not affected,
no matter how much Chakra
I hit him with...
(濡羅吏)ククク…。
お前は 柔拳使いのようだが
相手が悪かったな。
It seems that you use
the Gentle Fist.
I'm a bad match for you.
さっきのボウヤに助けを求める？
Do you want that boy to help you?
No. If I call Kiba-kun,
it'll be just what he wants...
《ダメ… ここでキバ君を呼んでも
狙い撃ちになるだけ》
アハッ！
(ヒナタ)キャ～ッ！
ヒナタ!!
Hinata!
ヒナタ！
(キバ)クソッ！
なんか手はねえのかよ！
Crap! Isn't there something I can do?!
(赤丸)キューン。
そうか！ これなら
うまくいくかもしれねえ！
That's it!
This just might work!
Let's go, Akamaru!
行くぞ 赤丸！
ワン！
(牛頭)こっちだ！
ぐわっ！
Over here!
さっきより速い！
He's even faster than before...
(カカシ)だが攻撃は直線的。
かえって見切りは容易だ！
But his attacks are straightforward!
They're easy to read!
フン。
なに!?
What?!
間に合うか!?
Will I make it?!
(麒児)とどめを刺せ 濡羅吏！
Finish her off, Nurari!
(濡羅吏)了解。
Understood.
な… 何だ!?
Wh-What's this...?!
(キバ)もういっちょ いくぜ！
牙通牙!!
Once more!
Fang Over Fang!
K-Kiba-kun...?
キバ君…。
(濡羅吏)何だ これは!?
What is this?!
Hinata!
ヒナタ！
ワン！
(キバ)わりいな 遅くなっちまって。
Sorry I'm late.
H-Hey, are you all right?
おい 大丈夫か？
キバ君 どうやって…？
Kiba, how did you find me?
Well, I used the spin of
my Fang Over Fang
あぁ。 牙通牙の回転で この辺りの
空気を かき回してやったのさ。
to stir the air around me.
ついでに
辺りの風通しもよくしたら➡
Once the air circulation improved,
that annoying smoke cleared up.
やっと クソ忌々しい煙幕が
晴れたってわけだ。
視覚と嗅覚さえ戻れば
こっちのもんだぜ！
With my sense of sight and smell back,
we've got the advantage.
さんざん好き勝手しやがって！
テメエら 覚悟しやがれ!!
You may have done
whatever you wanted before,
but prepare yourselves!
(麒児)覚悟？ どっちが？
Are you sure we're  the ones
who should prepare ourselves?
Crap! Others were waiting
to ambush us...?
クソーッ！
まだ伏兵が いやがったのか！
(麒児)フンッ 残念だったな。
Too bad.
まぁ これで
お前らの手の内は わかった。
Well, now that we know all about you...
We're going to kill them
with our next attack!
次で仕留めるぞ!!
(濡羅吏たち)承知！
- Understood!
What?!
なに!?
That's impossible...
そんなバカな！
This feeling. We're surrounded...
(麟児)この反応 囲まれてやがる。
(鬼霧)おい アニキ！
鬼霧 煙幕だ！
Hey, Aniki?!
Kigiri, a smoke screen! Retreat!
撤退するぞ！
なに!?
What?!
ゴホッ ゴホッ！
テメエら どういうつもり…。
What the hell are they doing?
It seems that the enemy
has good senses as well.
(シノ)敵も 優れた感知能力を
持っているようだ。
Shino!
(キバ)シノ！
How unfortunate...
(シノ)惜しいことをしたものだ。
(シノ)もう少しで 包囲網が
完成するところだったが…。
I was just about to finish casting
a net around them...
ヘッ。
Is everyone all right?
(カカシ)みんな無事か？
Kakashi-sensei!
(キバ)カカシ先生。
We're all together.
(カカシ)これで 全員揃ったな。
(キバ)あぁ だが ヒナタが…。
Yeah. But Hinata is...
どうだ？ 動けそうか？
How is it? Can you move?
はい なんとか… うぅ！
Yes, somewhat...
クゥ～ン。
先生
あのでかいヤツは やったのか？
Sensei, did you get that big guy?
No...
(カカシ)いや 仕留め損ねた。
I couldn't get him...
(キバ)そうか…
こっちも逃げられたぜ。
I see...
They got away from us too.
じゃあ まだ 戦闘は
終わっていない。
Then the battle's not over yet.
近くに あの術の使い手が
いるはずだ。
There should be
another Jutsu user nearby...
Oh? How interesting.
(紅蓮)へぇ おもしろいな。
I never expected my pursuer to
be Kakashi the Copy Ninja...
(紅蓮)まさか 追っ手が あの➡
コピー忍者のカカシだったとはね。
It may have been too much
for Gozu and Rinji.
牛頭や麟児には 荷が重すぎたか。
My preparation went well.
I guess it's my turn!
仕込みは上々
さて そろそろ私が出るか。
(幽鬼丸)母さま…。
Mother...
Oh my god! Oh my god!
oh my god oh my god
yesterday's mistake got me discouraged, but
kinou no shippai de kojiketatte
Thank you! Thank you!
gottsuanda gottsuanda
my new clothes got splashed with some sauce, wow
onyuu no fuku ni sousu ga hanete wao
don't mind, don't mind, if I stay feeling like this I'll have a tear in my eyes
donmai donmai shizunda mama ja namida mo my eyes
I may be hungry and angry
donna ni hangurii de angurii demo
but I'll grab a bowl to eat and start dancing!
donburi kutte danshingu
We'll always be pals my brother!
orera itsumo demo nakama daro burazaa
hit me with an upwind or strong wind or a storm I'm ready so come on!
tatoe gyarufuu kyoufuu arashi ga fuitemo bacchikoi kamon
we may be apart but we'll still be under the same sky
hanaretetemo onaji sora no shita de
so smile and hang on
saa waratte funbatte
lets do it do it do it do it
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
even if morning doesn't come, yay yay
tatoe asa ga konakutatte yay yay
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
we'll still watch the dream together, yay yay
kimi to tomo ni yume wo miru ze yay yay
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
no matter what, don't ever, ever give up, yay yay
nani ga nandemo aa demo kou demo akirameru na yay yay
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
morning will always come after night, yay yay
donna yoru mo asa wa kuru ze yay yay
nanananana
Next Episode
Say Captain Yamato...
うん おいしい！
(サクラ)ヒナタ！
are you sure we're closing in
on Kakashi-sensei's team?
あっ！
こんなところで何やってるの？
If things are going according to plan,
he should have left some sign.
べ 別に なんでもないよ。
But I don't see anything like that here.
はは～ん バレンタインチョコね
誰にあげるの？
Geez! Did they forget that
we're following right behind them?!
そ それは…。
Of course not!
でも これじゃダメ！ いい？
We should assume something happened
to the search team!
バレンタインデーってのは
チョコで 勝負が決まるのよ。
Sai, do reconnaissance from the sky.
私に任せなさい！
I have a bad feeling about this.
(サクラ)滋養強壮に マンネンダケの粉。
The Labyrinth of
Distorted Reflection
Next Time:
"The Labyrinth of Distorted Reflection"
疲労回復に ドラゴンガメのエキス。
それから 美肌効果に
ネバイモのすりおろし！
できた～！
- It's good!
- Hinata!
(サクラ)というわけで 義理チョコ。
What are you doing here?
(キバ)何が 「というわけ」
なんだよ？
N-Nothing.
あの 怖くて渡せなかったの。
ご ごめんなさい！
A Valentine's Day chocolate.
Who are you giving it to?
- W-Well...
- But this isn't enough!
あ～ ちょっと！ ヒナタ～！
ん？ 誰に渡せなかったって？
Listen well! Valentine's Day is...
a battle that's determined
by the chocolate!
ナルトだろ。
Leave this to me!
まっ いっか！
いっただきま～…。
Lingzhi powder for nourishment.
Dragon Turtle extract to relieve fatigue.
(キバ)うわっ！ なんじゃこりゃ!?
And grated glutinous yam for healthy skin.
Complete!
So anyway,
here are some lovely chocolates!
What do you mean, "so anyway"?
Umm... I was too afraid
to give it to him...
S-Sorry.
Oh, wait! Hinata--!
Who couldn't she give this to?
It's probably Naruto.
Oh well. Let's eat!
What the hell is this?!